Wow...
So this is Lyrical Monasterio...
Even a hopeless girl like me,
can definitely become a sparkling idol here...
Let's see...
Where's the entrance ceremony venue...?
Hey！
Eek!
Are you a freshman too?
I-I'm...
Wait, she vanished?!
Ah, over there!
Sup!
I'm Santi! I came from DragEm...
I mean, Dragon Empire!
A gyaru...! How scary!
What about you?
M-My name is Luvna.
I'm a ghost from Dark States...
Whenever I get nervous or embarrassed, I turn invisible.
A ghost?!
That explains it!
She's so close...!
Is she gonna mug me?!
Your skin is so nice!
Must be because Dark States doesn't get much UV light, huh?
Ah, haha... Yeah...
I've seen that phrase:
"Gyarus who are nice to otaku" online before...
Could she actually just be a nice person...?
Luvna-cchi!
Ah, yes!
Alright!
Starting today, we're friends!
Friends with me...? Is this...
Ababababababa!
Ah, my bad!
I forgot I'm a Thunder Dragon.
Ghost Meets Gal!